<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Love_Canada</string> <string name="Niagra">"Niagara Falls is Canada's most famous natural attraction, bringing in millions of visitors each year. Located just over an hour's drive from Toronto, along the American border, these massive falls drop approximately 57 meters. You can see the falls at an astoundingly close distance from several key points.

Niagara Falls and the Niagara Gorge have been attracting tourists and daredevils for well over a century. Between the mid-19th and mid-20th centuries there were numerous attempts to plunge over the falls in various types of homemade boats and barrels. This, along with tightrope walkers and other spectacles, led to the adjacent town of Niagara Falls developing a carnival type atmosphere that still persists today. Families will enjoy a walk down Niagara's outrageous Clifton Hill leading to the gorge and falls."</string>
<string name="Cntower"> "The CN Tower is a 553.3 m-high (1,815.3 ft) concrete communications and observation tower located in Downtown Toronto, Ontario, Canada. Built on the former Railway Lands, it was completed in 1976. Its name "CN" originally referred to Canadian National, the railway company that built the tower."</string>
    <string name="trondheim"> "Trondheim, historically Kaupangen, Nidaros and Trondhjem, is a city and municipality in Trøndelag county, Norway. It has a population of 199,039 (27/02/2020), and is the third most populous municipality in Norway, although the fourth largest urban area."</string>
    <string name="lakelouise">"A resort for all seasons, offering stunning views of the Canadian Rockies, the Lake Louise Inn brings the best of Banff National Park to our guests’ doorstep. Unwind and connect with yourself, friends, family, and nature within this pristine mountain retreat.

CONNECT THROUGH NATURE."</string>
    <string name="whistler">"Whistler (Squamish language: Sḵwiḵw) is a resort municipality in the southern Pacific Ranges of the Coast Mountains in the province of British Columbia, Canada, approximately 125 km (78 mi) north of Vancouver and 36 km (22 mi) south of the town of Pemberton."</string>

<string name="banffnational">"Banff National Park (French: Parc national Banff) is Canada's oldest national park and was established in 1885. Located in Alberta's Rocky Mountains, 110–180 kilometres (68–112 mi) west of Calgary, Banff encompasses 6,641 square kilometres (2,564 sq mi)[2] of mountainous terrain, with many glaciers and ice fields, dense coniferous forest, and alpine landscapes. "</string>
<string name="stanleypark">"Welcome to Stanley Park, Vancouver's first, largest, and most beloved urban park!

    Stanley Park is a magnificent green oasis in the midst of the urban landscape of Vancouver

Explore the 400-hectare natural West Coast rainforest and enjoy scenic views of water, mountains, sky, and majestic trees along Stanley Park's famous Seawall.</string>
    <string name="butchart">"The Butchart Gardens is a group of floral display gardens in Brentwood Bay, British Columbia, Canada, located near Victoria on Vancouver Island. The gardens receive over a million visitors each year. The gardens have been designated a National Historic Site of Canada."</string>
    <string name="CapeBretron">"cape Breton Island (French: île du Cap-Breton—formerly Île Royale; Scottish Gaelic: Ceap Breatainn or Eilean Cheap Breatainn; Mi'kmaq: Unamaꞌkik; or simply Cape Breton) is an island on the Atlantic coast of North America and part of the province of Nova Scotia, Canada."</string>
<string name="peggy">"Nova Scotia is home to over 160 historic lighthouses and these majestic beacons can be found throughout the province. Some of our lighthouses are world famous! Peggy's Cove Lighthouse, also known as Peggy's Point Lighthouse, is one of Nova Scotia’s most well-known lighthouses and may be the most photographed in Canada. Located in the quaint fishing village of Peggy’s Cove along the South Shore, Peggy’s Point Lighthouse was built in 1915."</string>
<string name="waterton">"Waterton is waiting for you ... Rocky Mountains and crystal clear lakes, acres of wildflowers, miles of pristine trails and centuries of fascinating history. It's waiting with a rugged natural beauty you won't see anywhere else in this world. Stroll our flower-lined streets, picnic along our shorelines, golf our courses and explore our village boutiques. Relax in our of our lakeside or mountain-view suites and enjoy fine dining that celebrates fresh local ingredients. Welcome to Waterton Lakes National Park."</string>
    <string name="Capilano">"The Capilano Suspension Bridge is a simple suspension bridge crossing the Capilano River in the District of North Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada. The current bridge is 140 metres (460 ft) long and 70 metres (230 ft) above the river."</string>
    <string name="tremblant">"Mont-Tremblant is a city in the Laurentian Mountains of Quebec, Canada, approximately 130 kilometres (81 mi) northwest of Montreal and 140 kilometres (87 mi) northeast of Ottawa, Ontario. The current municipality with city status was formed in 2000."</string>
    <string name="IcefieldSkywalk">"The Columbia Icefield is the largest ice field in the Rocky Mountains.[1] Located in the Canadian Rockies astride the Continental Divide along the border of British Columbia and Alberta, Canada, the ice field lies partly in the northwestern tip of Banff National Park and partly in the southern end of Jasper National Park."</string>
<string name="MountLogan">" Mount Logan (/ˈloʊɡən/) is the highest mountain in Canada and the second-highest peak in North America, after Denali. The mountain was named after Sir William Edmond Logan, a Canadian geologist and founder of the Geological Survey of Canada (GSC). Mount Logan is located within Kluane National Park Reserve[5] in southwestern Yukon, less than 40 kilometres (25 mi) north of the Yukon–Alaska border. Mount Logan is the source of the Hubbard and Logan glaciers."</string>
</resources>
